<resources>

    <string name="app_name"></string>
    <string name="aboutUsText">The number one place to find certified
        Android developers for your project . Our team is diverse, creative, and highly qualified.
    We take pride in developing high quality apps for the modern world through design and functionality.
     Coding Heroes developers deliver all your project developing needs. </string>

    <string name="coding_heroes_headerTxt">CODING \nHEROES</string>
    <string name="our_heroes_text">Our Heroes</string>
    <string name="image_view_profile_description">profile photo goes here</string>
    <string name="personal_name_textview_description">Replace with your own name</string>
    <string name="profile_name">YOUR NAME</string>
    <string name="profile_aboutyou_textview_description">Add your biography</string>
    <string name="aboutyou_text"></string>
    <string name="profile_quote_description">Add a quote here</string>
    <string name="profile_quotetext">My Quote/favorite quote - by someone</string>
    <string name="profiel_github_button_description">image button that will be used for github links</string>
    <string name="main_groupPhoto_imageview_description">image view that holds the group photo</string>
    <string name="main_imageButton_navDescription">image button for navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink1">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/StoryApp</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink2">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/BankTeller</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink3">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/HW2Game</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubLink4">https://github.com/rosannaNaomy/Unit1_Assessment</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject1_name">GitHub project 1</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject2_name">GitHub project 2</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject3_name">GitHub project 3</string>
    <string name="naomyGitHubProject4_name">GitHub project 4</string>

    <string name="lola_github_project_1">project_1</string>
    <string name="lola_github_project_2">project_2</string>
    <string name="lola_github_project_3">project_3</string>
    <string name="lola_aboutMe_textview_description">Migrating from Nigeria to United States at the young age of 11, I was forced to adapt to a completely new way of life. Being raised by a single mother of three has taught me a lot about hard work, dedication and perseverance. After obtaining my Bachelor in Psychology and unable to find employment, I decided to become an Emergency Medical Technician. Unfortunately 2 years later, I got injured at the job and could no longer perform the necessary tasks required on the job. About a week after the injury, I found out I was pregnant. Feeling down and unsure of where to go next, I decided to join the workforce. My original plan was to simply find another healthcare job position in which I could somehow utilize my experiences and skills that I had already acquired. Sometimes we are unaware of what direction God chooses to take us and what path he uses to get us there. One day out the blue, I received an email from workforce about a program called Bridge-To-Tech. This program preps students for Tech Bootcamps. Never having done any form of coding, I decided to apply. Fortunately I got accepted and suddenly I realized how much I enjoyed coding. After the 2 month prep, I applied to Pursuit (formerly C4Q) and got accepted. Hence here I am now pursuing something that can potentially change the course of my future for the better. Being a woman and a minority, I would love to bridge that gap and have the opportunity to inspire others who are in my shoes. In conclusion, I would like to say, trust the process of your life and where it takes you. Things that seem like it was meant to break you can be simply be your blessings in disguise.</string>
    <string name="lola_profile_quoteText">"Anything worth doing, is worth doing well!" -by Kike(mother)</string>
    <string name="lola_profile_name">Omolola(Lola) Abudu</string>
    <string name="headerName_naomy">Naomy Portillo</string>
    <string name="quoteText_naomy">"Everything in this world is magic, except for the magician" - by Dr.Ford</string>
    <string name="bioText_naomy">Naomy Portillo is an Android development Fellow at Pursuit. Enrolled in a Google-funded software engineering program, gaining hands-on experience with Java, Android SDK, Git/GitHub, Data Structures, Algorithms, APIs, tech principles and culture via both team/individual projects, code reviews, and pair programming.

\nBorn and raised in Queens, before Pursuit I was double majoring in design and computer science at Queens College. </string>
    <string name="positionText">Software Developer</string>

    <string name="fribel_github_project1">Project 1</string>
    <string name="fribel_github_project2">Project 2</string>
    <string name="fribel_github_project3">Project 3</string>
    <string name="fribel_aboutMe_textview">Fribel has a background in design and customer service. Strong communications skills and a
    eye for design.Fribel  has taken over 10 mobile apps from concept to millions of users as the lead engineer of multiple teams in various companies,
        including his own. Before focusing full-time on Android apps, he worked for Google and CERN (home of the LHC particle accelerator)
        as well as various tech startups in NY. She has invaluable experience in all areas related to Android apps from design and coding to acquisition and growth.
        Visit her projects on Git to see her previous work. </string>
    <string name="fribel_profile_quoteText">"I do not fear computers"</string>
    <string name="fribel_profile_name">Fribel Guzman</string>

</resources>

